razzball.com 2011-10-07

# 

Privacy Policy Statement This is the web site of Razzball.com. We can be reached via e-mail at info@razzball.com or you can reach us by telephone at For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer's domain name and e-mail address (where possible). We collect no information on consumers who browse our Web page. With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences. With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, you can visit [Google's Advertising and Privacy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) page. From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. Upon request we provide site visitors with access to a description of information that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the above address. If you wish to opt out of Advertising companies tracking and tailoring advertisements to your surfing patterns you may do so at [Network Advertising Initiative](http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). Google uses the Doubleclick DART cookie to serve ads across it's Adsense network and you can get further information regarding the DART cookie at [Doubleclick](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) as well as opt out options at [Google's Privacy Center](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Privacy I respect your privacy and I am committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at Razzball.com. The following discloses how I gather and disseminate information for this Blog. RSS Feeds and Email Updates If a user wishes to subscribe to my RSS Feeds or Email Updates (powered by Feedburner), I ask for contact information such as name and email address. Users may opt-out of these communications at any time. Your personal information will never be sold or given to a third party. (You will never be spammed by me - ever.) Log Files and Stats Like most blogging platforms I use log files, in this case Statcounter. This stores information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring, exit and visited pages, platform used, date/time stamp, track user’s movement in the whole, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. Cookies A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. This blog doesn't use cookies. However, some of my business partners use cookies on this site (for example - advertisers). I can't access or control these cookies once the advertisers have set them. Links This Blog contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. I suggest my users be aware of this when they leave this blog and to read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Razzball.com. Advertisers I use outside ad companies to display ads on this blog. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the advertising companies and I do not have access to this information. I deal with the following advertising companies: Google Adsense and SportsFanLive. Please check the advertisers websites for respective privacy policies. Contact Information If you have any questions or concerns please contact Grey at info@razzball.com. This privacy policy updated November 2009.
